<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <VFEE_Archcount.label>ерцграф</VFEE_Archcount.label>
  <VFEE_Archcount.labelFemale>archcountess</VFEE_Archcount.labelFemale>
  <VFEE_Archcount.description>The Imperial title of archcount is bestowed upon those counts who have established impressive holdings, which are capable of supporting and entertaining important guests.</VFEE_Archcount.description>

  <VFEE_Marquess.label>маркіза</VFEE_Marquess.label>
  <VFEE_Marquess.labelFemale>marchioness</VFEE_Marquess.labelFemale>
  <VFEE_Marquess.description>The Imperial title of marquess is the second highest of the middle nobility. In the Empire, they control colonies that border the edge of Imperial space. During wartime, they can field fleets that either prevent the enemy from penetrating the borders or be the anvil to the hammer of supporting friendlies.</VFEE_Marquess.description>

  <VFEE_Archduke.label>ерцгерцог</VFEE_Archduke.label>
  <VFEE_Archduke.labelFemale>archduchess</VFEE_Archduke.labelFemale>
  <VFEE_Archduke.description>The Imperial title of archduke is bestowed upon dukes whose territory requires a competent retinue to maintain order. They are expected to host their own divisions as well as their training, and in peacetime can establish a minor House.</VFEE_Archduke.description>

  <VFEE_Magister.label>магістр</VFEE_Magister.label>
  <VFEE_Magister.labelFemale>magister</VFEE_Magister.labelFemale>
  <VFEE_Magister.description>The Imperial title of magister is the middle rank of high nobility. In the Empire, a magister is expected to coordinate the vast military capabilities of the Empire, in both peace and wartime, commanding in the presence of the Emperor.</VFEE_Magister.description>

  <VFEE_Despot.label>деспот</VFEE_Despot.label>
  <VFEE_Despot.labelFemale>despot</VFEE_Despot.labelFemale>
  <VFEE_Despot.description>The Imperial title of despot maintains dominion over a small star system of strategic importance. In the Empire, despots maintain an iron grip to ensure that resources continue to flow into Imperial coffers and factories, as their major House holds important administrative positions throughout the system of governance.</VFEE_Despot.description>

  <VFEE_HighStellarch.label>вищий стелларх</VFEE_HighStellarch.label>
  <VFEE_HighStellarch.description>The Imperial title of high stellarch represents dominion over multiple star systems, and control of one of the powerful Houses in the Empire. They answer to no one except the emperor and are expected to not only maintain but also expand their influence across space. Very few are capable of receiving this title, even fewer wish to take on the responsibilities.</VFEE_HighStellarch.description>


</LanguageData>